A Guide to the Lester M. Salamon Papers FA1868
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Related Projects, 1967-2021; 8; 25.25 Cubic Feet (67 containers)
  - The State of Nonprofit America - Progress Report, Mott Foundation and Nathan Cummings Foundation, 2000-2003 (Box 117, Folder 1232)
  - The State of Nonprofit America - Progress Report, Aspen Institute Carnegie Grant, 2002 (Box 117, Folder 1233)
  - The State of Nonprofit America - Author Publication Agreements, 2007-2009 (Box 117, Folder 1234)
  - The State of Nonprofit America - League of Orchestras/Operas, 2010 (Box 117, Folder 1235)
  - The State of Nonprofit America - Hudson Institute, 2009 (Box 117, Folder 1236)
  - The State of Nonprofit America - AAHSA Conference, 2008 (Box 117, Folder 1237)
  - The State of Nonprofit America - Nonprofit Overview and Trends, 2002 (Box 117, Folder 1238)
  - Kresge Foundation, 2007 (Box 118, Folder 1239)
  - Unraveling the Mystery of America's Resilient Sector - Alliance Leadership Conference, 2008 (Box 118, Folder 1240)
  - The State of the Sector Project - National Assembly, 2005 (Box 118, Folder 1241)
  - Nonprofit Finance Project - Colorado Nonprofit Association, 2006 (Box 118, Folder 1242)
  - The State of the Sector Grant Report, Mott Foundation, 2005 (Box 118, Folder 1243)
  - The Resilient Sector- Updates, 2005 (Box 118, Folder 1244)
  - Context of Nonprofit Management Revisions, 2010 (Box 118, Folder 1245)
  - State of the Sector Proofs - Chapter 1, 2012 (Box 118, Folder 1246)
  - The State of the Sector Project - Finances, 2000-2003 (Box 118, Folder 1247)
  - The State of the Sector Project - Volunteerism, 2005-2011 (Box 118, Folder 1248)
  - The State of the Sector Project - Professionalism, 2000-2009 (Box 118, Folder 1249)
  - The State of the Sector Project - Commercialism, 1997-2009 (Box 118, Folder 1250)
  - The State of the Sector Project - Civic Activism, 2003-2009 (Box 119, Folder 1251)
  - The State of the Sector Project - Volume 2 Strategy Meeting, 2003 (Box 119, Folder 1252)
  - The State of the Sector Project - Stewart, Education, 2010 (Box 119, Folder 1253)
  - The State of the Sector Project - Volume 2, Mark Chavez, 2008 (Box 119, Folder 1254)
  - The State of the Sector Project - Atul Dighe Draft, 2008 (Box 119, Folder 1255)
  - The State of the Sector Project - Brookings Institution, 2003 (Box 119, Folder 1256)
  - The State of the Sector Project - Brookings Author Questionnaire, undated (Box 119, Folder 1257)
  - The State of the Sector Project - Brookings Marketing and Promotion, 2003 (Box 119, Folder 1258)
  - The State of the Sector Project - Brookings Press Release, undated (Box 119, Folder 1259)
  - The State of the Sector Project - Praise for The State of the Nonprofit Sector, undated (Box 119, Folder 1260)
  - The State of the Sector Project - LipmanHearne Contract Extension, 2003 (Box 119, Folder 1261)
  - Federal Budgets and Charitable Organizations, 1995 (Box 119, Folder 1262)
  - The Nonprofit Sector and the Federal Budget, 1997 (Box 119, Folder 1263)
  - The Nonprofit Sector and the Federal Budget: President Clinton's FY 1998 Budget Proposal, 1997-1998 (Box 119, Folder 1264)
  - Nonprofits and the 104th Congress, 1994-1995 (Box 119, Folder 1265)
  - Nonprofit Law: Issues in Search of Resolution, undated (Box 120, Folder 1267)
  - The Nonprofit Sector and the Federal Budget in the 1990s - Draft, 1994 (Box 120, Folder 1269)
  - Comparative Nonprofit - Beyond NGOs: The Third Sector in Latin America, 2000 (Box 120, Folder 1270)
  - Comparative Nonprofit - Explaining Nonprofit Advocacy, 1995 (Box 120, Folder 1271)
  - Comparative Nonprofit - Comparative History and the Theory of Modernization, 1970 (Box 120, Folder 1272)
  - Comparative Nonprofit - NGOs and U.S. Foreign Policy, 1998 (Box 120, Folder 1273)
  - Toward a Civil Society: A New Paradigm for Solving Public Problems, 2001 (Box 120, Folder 1274)
  - Nonprofits and Democracy, 1998 (Box 120, Folder 1275)
  - Tales of the Field: Economic and Institutional Theories of the Nonprofit Organization in the Light of Cross-National Evidence, Sokolowski, 2000 (Box 120, Folder 1276)
  - NGO Development in Central an Eastern Europe: An Empirical Overview, undated (Box 120, Folder 1277)
  - Comparative Nonprofit - Susannah Morris Criticism, undated (Box 120, Folder 1278)
  - Comparative Nonprofit - NVSQ Reviews/Ru Symposium, 2019-2020 (Box 120, Folder 1279)
  - Volunteering - Ksenija Fronovic Book, 2008-2020 (Box 121, Folder 1281)
  - UN Handbook Paper, Association for Research in Income and Wealth, 2000 (Box 121, Folder 1282)
  - Amsterdam Volunteering Paper, 2001 (Box 121, Folder 1283)
  - Florini Book Comments, 2001 (Box 121, Folder 1285)
  - Arnova Impact Paper, 2001 (Box 121, Folder 1287)
  - Volunteering in a Cross-National Perspective: Evidence from 24 Countries, 2001-2004 (Box 121, Folder 1288)
  - Volunteering in a Cross-National Perspective: Evidence from 27 Countries, 2002 (Box 121, Folder 1289)
  - Law Paper, 2002 (Box 121, Folder 1291)
  - Foreign Policy, 2002 (Box 121, Folder 1292)
  - Playing the NGO Card, 2001 (Box 121, Folder 1293)
  - The Real Meaning of September 11th for Nonprofits, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 1294)
  - Nonprofit Impact Literature, 1996-2002 (Box 122, Folder 1297)
  - The Nonprofit Sector in Global Perspective - Draft, 2002-2003 (Box 122, Folder 1298)
  - Encyclopedia of Philanthropy in the U.S. - Contributor Guidelines, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 1299)
  - Institutional Roots of Volunteering, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 1300)
  - Brazil Trip - Presentation Notes, Summaries, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 1303)
  - South Africa - Phase IIB, 2003 (Box 122, Folder 1307)
  - OECD Statistician Paper, 2002-2003 (Box 122, Folder 1308)
  - Civil Society in Global Perspective - Chapter 1, 2002-2003 (Box 123, Folder 1311)
  - Civil Society in Global Perspective: Findings from the Johns Hopkins Comparative Nonprofit Sector Project, 2003 (Box 123, Folder 1312)
  - Global Civil Society II Intro Revisions, 2002-2003 (Box 123, Folder 1313)
  - Social Origins - Power and Path Dependence, 2002-2003 (Box 123, Folder 1314)
  - Comparative Method Literature, 1971-2000 (Box 123, Folder 1316)
  - Civil Society in Central Europe, Zimmerman - Foreword by Salamon, 2003 (Box 123, Folder 1317)
  - Comparative Nonprofit Data with Volunteers, undated (Box 123, Folder 1318)
  - Accounting for Nonprofit Impact - Draft, 2004 (Box 123, Folder 1319)
  - UN Project - CIVINET Powerpoint, undated (Box 123, Folder 1320)
  - Global Civil Society - Chapter 1 Revisions, 2004 (Box 123, Folder 1322)
  - Interview, Alliance Magazine - Edits, 2004 (Box 124, Folder 1325)
  - Globalization and the Civil Society Sector, Rockefeller Center Volume, 2003-2004 (Box 124, Folder 1326)
  - Global Civil Society II - Briefing, Skoll Forum, undated (Box 124, Folder 1327)
  - Global Civil Society - Index, 2004 (Box 124, Folder 1328)
  - Global Civil Society, Volume 2, 2004 (Box 124, Folder 1329)
  - Myths of Global Civil Society Notes, undated (Box 124, Folder 1330)
  - UN Handbook Pilot Test, Helen Tice, 2002 (Box 124, Folder 1332)
  - Phase IIB - Comparative Nonprofit Data, 2002-2003 (Box 124, Folder 1333)
  - European Foundation Centre (EFC) - Handbook of Foundations, 2003-2005 (Box 124, Folder 1334)
  - Volunteering Data, 2005 (Box 124, Folder 1335)
  - Comparative Nonprofit - Master File, 37 Countries, 2005 (Box 124, Folder 1336)
  - Satellite Account of Nonprofit Institutions, Belgium Account, 2000-2001 (Box 124, Folder 1337)
  - Need for Nonprofit Institution Data, 2005 (Box 125, Folder 1338)
  - The Nonprofit Sector in Comparative Perspective, Version 5 - Comments, 2003 (Box 125, Folder 1339)
  - The Nonprofit Sector in Comparative Perspective - Drafts, 2006 (Box 125, Folder 1340)
  - Government-Nonprofit Relations in International Perspective - Comments, 2006 (Box 125, Folder 1341)
  - SNA Letter, 2005 (Box 125, Folder 1342)
  - Voluntary Sector Initiative (VSI) - Canada Evaluation, undated (Box 125, Folder 1343)
  - Measuring Civil Society Presentation, 2005 (Box 125, Folder 1346)
  - FP 7 Finances, Final, 2017 (Box 125, Folder 1347)
  - Civil Society and Democracy: Prerequisite, Impediment, or Irrelevance?, 2002-2007 (Box 126, Folder 1351)
  - SNA News, SNA Update Project, 2006 (Box 126, Folder 1352)
  - Inter-American Development Bank Foundation, 2007 (Box 126, Folder 1355)
  - Putting Nonprofits Institutions and Volunteer Work into the Measurement of Economic Performance and Social Progress - Stiglitz Report, 2009 (Box 126, Folder 1359)
  - The European Social Economy, Social Enterprise - Ciriec Paper, 2001-2008 (Box 126, Folder 1360)
  - Volunteering in the European Union - Euro C Report, 2010 (Box 126, Folder 1361)
  - USAID Democracy and Government Framwork, 2010 (Box 126, Folder 1365)
  - Global Civil Society (GCS) III - Netherlands, 2011 (Box 127, Folder 1371)
  - ILO Manual on Volunteer Work - Becchetti Comments, 2011 (Box 127, Folder 1373)
  - Relation Goods, Sociability, and Happiness, Becchettie, Pelloni, and Rossetti, 2008 (Box 127, Folder 1374)
  - IDB Regional Project, 2011 (Box 127, Folder 1377)
  - TechSoup/Guidestar Partnership, 2010-2012 (Box 127, Folder 1380)
  - Portugal NPI Report, 2012 (Box 127, Folder 1381)
  - Center for Civil Society Studies - Overview, 2009-2012 (Box 127, Folder 1382)
  - Beyond GDP, 2011 (Box 127, Folder 1383)
  - Mexico Nonprofit Report, 2012 (Box 127, Folder 1384)
  - Lending Age, 2012 (Box 128, Folder 1387)
  - International Work, Center for Civil Society Studies International Overview, undated (Box 128, Folder 1388)
  - Russia Chapter, 2012 (Box 128, Folder 1389)
  - Mexican-American Foundation Prologue, 2012 (Box 128, Folder 1392)
  - European Volunteer Measurement Project Workshop, 2011 (Box 128, Folder 1393)
  - Volunteering and Aging, Warsaw Conference, 2012 (Box 128, Folder 1394)
  - Eurostat ESA Meeting, 2010-2012 (Box 128, Folder 1396)
  - World Bank Partnership for Social Accountability, Washington, D.C., 2012 (Box 128, Folder 1397)
  - Volunteering and Aging, 2012 (Box 128, Folder 1398)
  - NWO Dekker Proposal, 2012 (Box 128, Folder 1399)
  - Turkey Def. Paper, 2012 (Box 128, Folder 1400)
  - Mongolia, 2012 (Box 128, Folder 1401)
  - Measuring Civil Society and Volunteering, UN Handbook, ISTR Paper, 2012 (Box 128, Folder 1402)
  - ISTR Volunteer Paper, 2012 (Box 128, Folder 1403)
  - European Economic and Social Committee: Statistical Tools for Measuring Volunteering, 2013 (Box 128, Folder 1405)
  - UN Handbook - Blue Book, 2013 (Box 128, Folder 1406)
  - Civil Society Bibliography, 2013 (Box 128, Folder 1407)
  - Ireland Volunteering, 2013 (Box 128, Folder 1408)
  - International Labour Organization (ILO) Redefining Work, 2013 (Box 129, Folder 1409)
  - Hungary Volunteering Data, 2012 (Box 129, Folder 1410)
  - NESsT Social Enterprise Project, 2013 (Box 129, Folder 1411)
  - Social Economy Paper, 2010-2013 (Box 129, Folder 1412)
  - Comparative Nonprofit Project - Turkey, 2015-2016 (Box 129, Folder 1413)
  - International Labour Organization (ILO) Work Revision, 2013 (Box 129, Folder 1414)
  - SNA and Philanthropy, 2014 (Box 129, Folder 1415)
  - Comparative Nonprofit Project - Effects Memo, 2015 (Box 129, Folder 1416)
  - Rotary International Proposal, 2015 (Box 129, Folder 1417)
  - UN Handbook - 16 Country Report, 2013 (Box 129, Folder 1418)
  - UN Handbook - Morocco, 2012 (Box 129, Folder 1419)
  - Global Civil Society III - Country Chapter Notes, 2015-2016 (Box 129, Folder 1421)
  - Closing the Gap: Volunteering North and South, undated (Box 129, Folder 1422)
  - A Cross-Country Analysis of Nonprofit Sector Growth, Voluntas - Draft, undated (Box 129, Folder 1423)
  - Volunteering: North and South, Butcher Book, 2017 (Box 129, Folder 1425)
  - TSI Project Book, 2014 (Box 129, Folder 1426)
  - UN Volunteers Report, 2017 (Box 129, Folder 1427)
  - Social Economy, 2011-2015 (Box 130, Folder 1428)
  - UN Handbook - Revisions, 2014-2017 (Box 130, Folder 1429)
  - UN Handbook - Backup Revisions, 2013-2015 (Box 130, Folder 1430)
  - Comparative Nonprofit Project - Phase II Data Contacts, 2001 (Box 130, Folder 1431)
  - Organisation for Economic Co-Operation and Development (OECD) Seminar, 2015-2017 (Box 130, Folder 1432)
  - Allies or Adversaries: NGOs and the State of Africa - Book Review, 2018 (Box 130, Folder 1433)
  - National Survey Report, 1983 (Box 130, Folder 1434-1435)
  - Survey Data - All Sites, 1982-1984 (Box 131, Folder 1436)
  - All Site Data, 1984 (Box 131, Folder 1437)
  - RD I Crosstabs - Wout Chi Square - Seyong Lee, 1992 (Box 131, Folder 1438)
  - Seyong Lee - RD I, 1992 (Box 131, Folder 1439)
  - Foundation Investment Results Study, 1986 (Box 131, Folder 1440)
  - Foundation Investment Report - Revisions, 1987 (Box 131, Folder 1441)
  - Managing Foundation Investments, Harvard Club, 1985 (Box 131, Folder 1442-1443)
  - Common Fund, 1986-1987 (Box 131, Folder 1444)
  - Managing Foundation Assets, Salamon and Voytek, 1988 (Box 131, Folder 1445)
  - Foundation Study, 1987 (Box 132, Folder 1446)
  - Foundation Administrative Expense Study, Council on Foundations, 1987 (Box 132, Folder 1447)
  - Foundation Center, Foundation Today, 1987 (Box 132, Folder 1448)
  - Center for Civil Society Studies (CCSS) - Future, 2004 (Box 132, Folder 1449)
  - Arnova Award for Leadership in Nonprofit and Voluntary Action Research, 2004 (Box 132, Folder 1450)
  - Independent Sector, undated (Box 132, Folder 1451)
  - New Frontiers of Philanthropy - Table of Contents - Final, 2013 (Box 132, Folder 1452)
  - Nonprofit Insurance Alliance, 2020 (Box 132, Folder 1453)
  - Penalty Assets, 2020-2021 (Box 132, Folder 1454)
  - Voluntas - Research Methods, 2020-2021 (Box 132, Folder 1455)
  - Luxembourg Handbook Implementation, 2019-2020 (Box 132, Folder 1456)
  - Op-Eds and Press, 2020 (Box 132, Folder 1457)
  - Global Civil Society III - Johns Hopkins University Press, 2018 (Box 132, Folder 1458)
  - Russia Outsourcing Study, 2020-2021 (Box 132, Folder 1459)
  - Europe TSE Handbook Implementation Project, 2015-2017 (Box 133, Folder 1462)
  - UN Handbook - ISTR Working Group, 2020-2021 (Box 133, Folder 1463)
  - State of the Sector - Intro Chapter Notes, undated (Box 133, Folder 1464)
  - State of the Sector - Chapter Tracking System, 2021 (Box 133, Folder 1465)
  - State of the Sector - Preface, 2002 (Box 133, Folder 1466)
  - State of the Sector - Abramson, 2000-2001 (Box 133, Folder 1467)
  - State of America's Nonprofit Sector- Brad Gray, Mark Schlesinger, 2000-2001 (Box 133, Folder 1469)
  - Elizabeth Boris, 2000-2001 (Box 133, Folder 1470)
  - Ten Basic Responsibilities of Nonprofit Board, Richard T. Ingram, 2003 (Box 133, Folder 1472)
  - Nonprofit and Voluntary Sector Quarterly (NVSQ) Reviews, 2020 (Box 133, Folder 1476)
  - Openness and Corruption Prevention, Central Asia - FDI Pro and Grant Letter, Uzbekistan, 2017-2019 (Box 133, Folder 1477)
  - Brazil Trip, 2019 (Box 133, Folder 1479)
  - Resilient Sector - Update, 2018-2019 (Box 133, Folder 1480)
  - La Caixa Case Study, 2018-2019 (Box 133, Folder 1482)
  - Global Civil Society - Mott Foundation, 2019 (Box 133, Folder 1484)
  - Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS) and Aspen Data Group, 2005-2020 (Box 133, Folder 1485)
  - Methodology of Regional Selection, Regional Grant Program, MED Paper, 2021 (Box 134, Folder 1486)
  - FP7 Third Sector Impact - Final Project Plan, 2013 (Box 134, Folder 1487)
  - Tools Workbook - Legal Coding Scheme, undated (Box 134, Folder 1488)
  - Thailand Legal Chapter, 1996 (Box 134, Folder 1489)
  - The Nonprofit Sector and Democracy: Identifying the Research Question, Aspen Institute and Nonprofit Research Fund, 1993 (Box 134, Folder 1490)
  - International Monetary Fund (IMF), 2005 (Box 134, Folder 1491)
  - Uzbekistan DFI Workshop, 2017-2019 (Box 134, Folder 1492)
  - Luxembourg Workshop on the Implementation of Satellite Accounts for the Third or Social Economy (TSE) Sector, 2019 (Box 134, Folder 1495)
  - Correspondence, 2016-2020 (Box 138, Folder 1526)
  - Rethinking Corporate Social Engagement - Lessons from Latin America, undated (Box 138, Folder 1527)
  - Salamon Data - Buck Trust Case, 1980-1986 (Box 138, Folder 1530-1531)
  - Resume and CV, 1981-1986 (Box 139, Folder 1532)
  - Nonprofit Issues Forum Flyer - Keynote Speaker Lester Salamon, 2012 (Box 139, Folder 1535)
  - Aaron Wildavsky Award, Johns Hopkins University Gazette, 2012 (Box 139, Folder 1538)
  - Aaron Wildavsky Award, Partners in Public Service, 2012 (Box 155)
  - International Fellows in Philanthropy Program, Johns Hopkins University - Celebrating 10 Years, 1998 (Box 139, Folder 1540)
  - X Giornata della Fondazione, 2010 (Box 139, Folder 1541)
  - Il volunariato e il futuro del "Welfare State" spunti di riflessione, 1989 (Box 139, Folder 1546)
  - Partners in Public Service - Book Cover, undated (Box 139, Folder 1547)
  - Economic Development and Minority Landowners, Duke-OMBE Land Project, 1976 (Box 139, Folder 1548)
  - New Tools Project, 1985-1991 (Box 139, Folder 1549)
  - Postcards, undated (Box 139, Folder 1550)
  - Nonprofit Economic Development Transition Team Subcommittee, 2014 (Box 139, Folder 1551)
- Photographs, 1990-2001; 9; 3.61 Cubic Feet (10 containers)
  - Urban Fellow Conference, Prague, 1991 (Box 140, Folder 1552)
  - Philanthropy Fellows Conference, Israel, 1991 (Box 140, Folder 1553)
  - Philanthropy Fellows Conference, Lille, France, 1991 June (Box 140, Folder 1554)
  - Moscow, 1991 October (Box 140, Folder 1555-1556)
  - Italy, Budapest, 1991 October (Box 140, Folder 1557)
  - Florida Trip, Bologna CNP, Third Sector Interns, Mallorca, 1992 (Box 140, Folder 1558)
  - Third Sector Project, Moscow and Israel Fellows Conference, 1992 (Box 140, Folder 1559)
  - Urban Fellows, Finland, 1992 (Box 141, Folder 1560)
  - Israel, 1992 (Box 141, Folder 1561)
  - Israel, Emmett Carson, 1992 (Box 141, Folder 1562)
  - Conference, 1992 (Box 141, Folder 1563)
  - Florida Hurricane, 1992 (Box 141, Folder 1564)
  - Egypt, 1992 January (Box 141, Folder 1565)
  - Philanthropy Fellows Conference, Israel, 1992 July (Box 141, Folder 1566)
  - Philanthropy Fellows Conference, Israel - Ali Assad, 1992 (Box 141, Folder 1567)
  - Fellows, Ghana, 1993 (Box 141, Folder 1568)
  - Ghana, 1993 (Box 141, Folder 1569)
  - Amsterdam Fellows Conference, 1994 (Box 141, Folder 1570)
  - 7 Day Follow Up Institute, Budapest, Hungary, 1995 Spring (Box 141, Folder 1571)
  - 9 Day Orientation Institute, Moscow, Russia, 1995 Summer (Box 141, Folder 1572)
  - U.S. Institute, 2nd Class, Russia, Bulgaria, Slovenia, 1995 (Box 142, Folder 1573-1575)
  - Urban Fellows Conference, Bucharest, Romania, 1996 (Box 142, Folder 1576)
  - IPS Picnic, 1996 (Box 142, Folder 1577)
  - HNTN Meeting, Krynica, Poland, 1996 (Box 142, Folder 1578)
  - 9 Day Orientation, 3rd Class, St. Petersburg, 1996 June (Box 142, Folder 1579)
  - Helmut's Farewell Dinner, 1998 (Box 142, Folder 1580)
  - Philanthropy Fellows Conference, Bengaluru, India, 1999 July (Box 142, Folder 1581)
  - Fellows, Melbourne, 2000 (Box 142, Folder 1582)
  - Follow Up Institute, Budapest, undated (Box 142, Folder 1583)
  - Gus Nossal Dinner and Miscellaneous, undated (Box 142, Folder 1584)
  - CNP Dublin Team Meeting, 1995 December (Box 143, Folder 1585)
  - CNP, Madrid, 1996 December (Box 143, Folder 1586)
  - Comparative Nonprofit Project (CNP), 1997 (Box 143, Folder 1587)
  - Comparative Nonprofit Project (CNP), 1997-1998 (Box 143, Folder 1588)
  - Comparative Nonprofit Project (CNP), Dublin, 1997 (Box 143, Folder 1589)
  - CNP Phase IIB Launch Meeting, Baltimore, 1998 December (Box 143, Folder 1590)
  - Comparative Nonprofit Sector, 1998-1999 (Box 143, Folder 1591)
  - CNP Team Meeting, Istanbul, 2000 (Box 143, Folder 1592)
  - ISTR Dublin, CNP, 2000 July (Box 143, Folder 1593)
  - CNP, Nairobi, 2001 March (Box 143, Folder 1594)
  - ISTR, Nairobi, 2001 November (Box 143, Folder 1595)
  - As dimensoes do 3 sector, da experiencia local a experiencia global, undated (Box 143, Folder 1596)
  - Caisses des Despots Event, Paris, undated (Box 143, Folder 1597)
  - TOTers in Novosibirsk, 1996 (Box 144, Folder 1598)
  - Fellows prior to 1999, 1996-1999 (Box 144, Folder 1599)
  - UN Handbook Meeting, 2000 (Box 144, Folder 1600)
  - Handbook Test Group, Consultative Group Meeting, 2001 July 8-9 (Box 144, Folder 1601)
  - 17th Annual Fellows in Philanthropy and Social Justice International Conference, undated (Box 144, Folder 1602-1604)
  - Conferences and Trips, 1994-1999 (Box 144, Folder 1605-1606)
  - Conferences and Trips, undated (Box 144, Folder 1607)
  - School of Advanced International Studies (SAIS), 1994 (Box 145, Folder 1608-1610)
  - 5th Annual Johns Hopkins International Philanthropy Fellows Conference - Album 1, 1993 July 5 (Box 145, Folder 1611-1612)
  - 5th Annual Johns Hopkins International Philanthropy Fellows Conference - Album 2, 1993 July 5 (Box 146, Folder 1613-1615)
  - 5th Annual Johns Hopkins International Philanthropy Fellows Conference - Album 3, 1993 July 5 (Box 146, Folder 1616-1618)
  - Salamon Headshots, undated (Box 147, Folder 1619)
  - Various Speaking Engagements, 1993-1996 (Box 147, Folder 1620)
  - Johns Hopkins University Center for Civil Society Studies Events, 1993-1994 (Box 147, Folder 1621)
  - Third Sector Project - First Internship Program, 1992 Spring (Box 147, Folder 1622)
  - Third Sector Project - Management Training Workshop, Vyskov, Czech, and Slovak Federal Republic, 1992 May 6-10 (Box 147, Folder 1623)
  - Third Sector Project - Management Training Workshop, Moscow Region, Russian Federation, 1992 June 21-25 (Box 147, Folder 1624-1625)
  - Third Sector Project - Management Training Workshop, Csopak, Hungary, 1992 November 8-12 (Box 147, Folder 1626)
  - Third Sector Project - Third Internship Program, 1993 Spring (Box 147, Folder 1627)
  - Third Sector Project - Intern Photographs with Governor Schaefer, undated (Box 147, Folder 1628)
  - Untitled Envelope, 2000 (Box 148, Folder 1629)
  - Untitled Envelope, undated (Box 148, Folder 1630)
  - Untitled Envelope, undated (Box 148, Folder 1631)
  - Untitled Envelope, undated (Box 148, Folder 1632)
  - Untitled Envelope, undated (Box 148, Folder 1633)
  - Untitled Envelope, undated (Box 148, Folder 1634)
  - Untitled Envelope, 1992 (Box 148, Folder 1635)
  - Untitled Envelope, 1990-1991 (Box 149, Folder 1636)
  - Untitled Envelope, 1992 August (Box 149, Folder 1637)
  - Miscellaneous, 1990-1992 (Box 149, Folder 1638)
  - Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 1639)
  - Miscellaneous, 1995-1996 (Box 149, Folder 1640)
  - Miscellaneous, 1992-1996 (Box 149, Folder 1641)
  - Holiday Parties, 1995; undated (Box 149, Folder 1642)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 149, Folder 1643)
  - Family, undated (Box 149, Folder 1644)
  - 16th Annual Johns Hopkins International Philanthropy Fellows Conference, Nairobi, Kenya, 2004 July 4-8 (Box 155, Folder 1645)
  - Untitled Photograph, Ephesus, 2010 (Box 155, Folder 1646)
  - 20th Annual Johns Hopkins International Urban Fellows Conference, Baltimore, 1990 June (Box 155, Folder 1647)
  - International Conference on Non-Profit Sector and Development, Tsinghua University, 1999 July 26-28 (Box 155, Folder 1648)
- Oversize Framed Material, undated; 10
  - Rethinking Corporate Social Engagements, undated (Frame 1)
    Framed cover of Salamon's book, Rethinking Corporate Social Engagement.
  - America's Nonprofit Sector, undated (Frame 2)
    Framed cover of America's Nonprofit Sector.
  - The State of Nonprofit America, undated (Frame 3)
    Framed cover of The State of Nonprofit America with accolades.
  - United Nations Handbook on National Accounting, undated (Frame 4)
    Framed cover of UN Handbook.
- Notebooks, 1990-2011 (Box 150)
- Index Cards - Bibliography, undated (Box 151)
  Contains nonprofit, tools, and tool of government action sections.
- Index Cards - Bibliography, undated (Box 152)
- Index Cards - Welfare Reform, PtP I, and PtP II, undated (Box 153)